Fred Crawford Papers
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 3. IOC File: Individual Research Correspondence, 3; Boxes: 19 - 23
  - Christopher Matheson, 1989 - 1998 (Folder 32, Box 21)
  - Harry W. Malm, 1991 (Folder 33, Box 21)
  - Mrs. Stella Matt, 1996 (Folder 34, Box 21)
  - Nedra McCloud, 1996 - 1997 (Folder 35, Box 21)
  - Molly McLean, 1997 (Folder 36, Box 21)
  - Mary E. McDonnell, 1991 (Folder 37, Box 21)
  - Robert Merrill, 1991 (Folder 38, Box 21)
  - Hack Miller, 1991 - 1996 (Folder 39, Box 21)
  - Maynard M. Miller, 1991 - 1997 (Folder 40, Box 21)
  - Gae Mitchell, 1991 (Folder 41, Box 21)
  - Herbert Moore, 1991 (Folder 42, Box 21)
  - Mrs. A. F. (Hurley) Mooy, 1996 (Folder 43, Box 21)
  - Edmund Morris, 1997 (Folder 44, Box 21)
  - James Morrison, 1991 - 1996 (Folder 45, Box 21)
  - William Morrison, 1991 (Folder 46, Box 21)
  - Richard Moulton, 1996 - 1998 (Folder 47, Box 21)
  - Bill D. Moyers, 1996 (Folder 48, Box 21)
  - Roger Mudd, 1996 (Folder 49, Box 21)
  - Thomas S. Murphy, 1991 - 1996 (Folder 50, Box 21)
  - 1, 1996 (Folder 1, Box 22)
  - 2, 1996 (Folder 2, Box 22)
  - 3, 1996 (Folder 3, Box 22)
  - 4, 1991 - 1996 (Folder 4, Box 22)
  - 5, 1996 (Folder 5, Box 22)
  - 6, 1991 (Folder 6, Box 22)
  - 7, 1991 (Folder 7, Box 22)
  - 8, 1991 (Folder 8, Box 22)
  - 9, 1991 - 1997 (Folder 9, Box 22)
  - 10, 1991 (Folder 10, Box 22)
  - 11, 1991 (Folder 11, Box 22)
  - 12, 1996 (Folder 12, Box 22)
  - 13, 1991 (Folder 13, Box 22)
  - 14, 1991 (Folder 14, Box 22)
  - 15, 1997 (Folder 15, Box 22)
  - 16, 1991 (Folder 16, Box 22)
  - 17, 1991 (Folder 17, Box 22)
  - 18, 1991 (Folder 18, Box 22)
  - 19, 1991 (Folder 19, Box 22)
  - 20, 1996 (Folder 20, Box 22)
  - 21, 1995 (Folder 21, Box 22)
  - 22, 1995 (Folder 22, Box 22)
  - 23, 1991 - 1994 (Folder 23, Box 22)
  - 24, 1996 (Folder 24, Box 22)
  - 25, 1991 (Folder 25, Box 22)
  - 26, 1991 (Folder 26, Box 22)
  - 27, 1991 - 1996 (Folder 27, Box 22)
  - 28, 1995 - 1996 (Folder 28, Box 22)
  - 29, 1991 (Folder 29, Box 22)
  - 30, 1995 - 1996 (Folder 30, Box 22)
  - 31, 1996 (Folder 31, Box 22)
  - 32, 1991 (Folder 32, Box 22)
  - 33, 1996 (Folder 33, Box 22)
  - 34, 1996 (Folder 34, Box 22)
  - 35, 1991 (Folder 35, Box 22)
  - 36, 1991 (Folder 36, Box 22)
  - 37, 1996 (Folder 37, Box 22)
  - 38, 1991 (Folder 38, Box 22)
  - 39, 1996 - 1997 (Folder 39, Box 22)
  - 40, 1997 (Folder 40, Box 22)
  - 41, 1996 (Folder 41, Box 22)
  - 42, 1996 (Folder 42, Box 22)
  - 43, 1991 (Folder 43, Box 22)
  - 44, 1991 - 1993 (Folder 44, Box 22)
  - 45, 1996 - 1997 (Folder 45, Box 22)
  - 46, 1996 (Folder 46, Box 22)
  - 47, 1990 - 1992 (Folder 47, Box 22)
  - 48, 1997 - 1998 (Folder 48, Box 22)
  - 49, 1991 - 1996 (Folder 49, Box 22)
  - 50, 1991 (Folder 50, Box 22)
  - 51, 1991 (Folder 51, Box 22)
  - 52, 1991 (Folder 52, Box 22)
  - 53, 1991 - 1992 (Folder 53, Box 22)
  - 54, 1996 (Folder 54, Box 22)
  - 55, 1997 (Folder 55, Box 22)
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr. [half of original file], 1996 - 1998 (Folder 1, Box 23)
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr. [half of original file], 1990 - 1995 (Folder 2, Box 23)
  - Marianna Thomas (Marianna Munn) [originally one file], 1997 - 1998 (Folder 3, Box 23)
  - Marianna Thomas (Marianna Munn) [originally one file], 1996 - 1997 (Folder 4, Box 23)
  - Marianna Thomas (Marianna Munn) [originally one file], 1995 - 1996 (Folder 5, Box 23)
  - Marianna Thomas (Marianna Munn) [originally one file], 1993 - 1995 (Folder 6, Box 23)
  - Marianna Thomas (Marianna Munn) [originally one file], 1991 - 1992 (Folder 7, Box 23)
  - Stephen W. Thomas, 1996 (Folder 8, Box 23)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Lloyd Tompkins, 1996 (Folder 9, Box 23)
  - Robert Trout, 1996 (Folder 10, Box 23)
  - Mrs. Upscheid, 1991 (Folder 11, Box 23)
  - Martina F. Van Ness, 1991 (Folder 12, Box 23)
  - Joe Vanderwalker, 1991 (Folder 13, Box 23)
  - Mike Wallace, 1996 (Folder 14, Box 23)
  - Barbara Walters, 1996 (Folder 15, Box 23)
  - Frieda Ward, 1991 (Folder 16, Box 23)
  - Geoffrey C. (Butler) Ward, 1996 (Folder 17, Box 23)
  - Bradford Washburn, 1997 (Folder 18, Box 23)
  - Thomas J. Watson, Jr., 1991 (Folder 19, Box 23)
  - Henry O. Wefing, 1991 - 1996 (Folder 20, Box 23)
  - Erica Weintraub (Austin), 1990 (Folder 21, Box 23)
  - Eric A. Weiss, 1991 - 1996 (Folder 22, Box 23)
  - Anthony Wellman, 1995 - 1996 (Folder 23, Box 23)
  - Jed Williamson, 1996 - 1997 (Folder 24, Box 23)
  - Barbara Winterton, 1991 (Folder 25, Box 23)
  - David Wolper, 1996 (Folder 26, Box 23)
  - Larry Wygant, undated (Folder 27, Box 23)
  - Ohrt Yeager, 1991 (Folder 28, Box 23)
  - Robert B. Yegge, 1991 (Folder 29, Box 23)
  - Mary - Bird Young, 1997 (Folder 30, Box 23)
  - Vince Young, 1996 (Folder 31, Box 23)
- 4. AC: Administrative Correspondence, 4; Boxes: 24 - 26
  - Advertising Agencies, 1997 (Folder 1, Box 24)
  - Advertising Club, 1996 (Folder 2, Box 24)
  - Air Force (FOIA) [Freedom of Information Act], 1993 - 1994 (Folder 3, Box 24)
  - American (Bender), 1996 - 1997 (Folder 4, Box 24)
  - Amherst College (Frost Library) correspondence, 1991 (Folder 5, Box 24)
  - Arbitron, 1995 (Folder 6, Box 24)
  - Army (FOIA) [Freedom of Information Act], 1993 - 1994 (Folder 7, Box 24)
  - Australia, Mitchell, NSW, 1996 (Folder 8, Box 24)
  - Australia National Library, 1996 - 1997 (Folder 9, Box 24)
  - Bohemian, 1996 (Folder 10, Box 24)
  - Bodleian [Library], 1991 (Folder 11, Box 24)
  - Bowdoin College Library correspondence, 1991 (Folder 12, Box 24)
  - Broadcast Pioneers, 1996 (Folder 13, Box 24)
  - Bucherer - Dietschi (Bibliotheca Afghanica), 1997 (Folder 14, Box 24)
  - BYU(Harold Bike Library) correspondence, 1991 (Folder 15, Box 24)
  - Capital Cities Communication, 1991 (Folder 16, Box 24)
  - James Earl Carter, 1991 (Folder 17, Box 24)
  - Carter P - L [Presidential Library] correspondence, 1991 (Folder 18, Box 24)
  - CBS, 1995 - 1996 (Folder 19, Box 24)
  - Chicago Historical Society, 1997 (Folder 20, Box 24)
  - CIA (FOIA) [Freedom of Information Act], 1993 - 1998 (Folder 21, Box 24)
  - University of Cincinnati, 1996 (Folder 22, Box 24)
  - Claremont (Honnold) correspondence, 1996 (Folder 23, Box 24)
  - Colorado Historical Society, 1991 - 1992 (Folder 24, Box 24)
  - Colorado Medical Society, 1997 (Folder 25, Box 24)
  - Colorado Ski Hall of Fame, 1991 (Folder 26, Box 24)
  - Colorado State Archives, 1991 (Folder 27, Box 24)
  - Columbia University Oral History Collection, 1996 (Folder 28, Box 24)
  - Congress, 1996 - 1997 (Folder 29, Box 24)
  - D.A.R. [Daughters of the American Revolution], 1996 (Folder 30, Box 24)
  - Dartmouth College [REW III], 1939 (Folder 31, Box 24)
  - Defense [Department] (FOIA) [Freedom of Information Act], 1993 (Folder 32, Box 24)
  - Denver P. L. [Public Library], 1991 (Folder 33, Box 24)
  - Eisenhower P - L [Presidential Library], 1991 (Folder 34, Box 24)
  - The Explorers Club, 1991 - 1996 (Folder 35, Box 24)
  - FDR [Franklin D. Roosevelt] Library, 1993 (Folder 36, Box 24)
  - Ferguson Memorial Library -CC [Cripple Creek], 1991 (Folder 37, Box 24)
  - FCC (FOIA) [Freedom of Information Act], 1993 - 1994 (Folder 38, Box 24)
  - Fish Library [Hamilton Fish], 1996 (Folder 39, Box 24)
  - Funk & Wagnalls, 1996 (Folder 40, Box 24)
  - Gerald R. Ford [person], 1991 - 1996 (Folder 41, Box 24)
  - Gerald R. Ford P-L [Presidential Library], 1991 - 1992 (Folder 42, Box 24)
  - Garst Museum, 1990 - 1998 (Folder 43, Box 24)
  - General Motors, 1996 (Folder 44, Box 24)
  - Georgetown University Library, 1991 (Folder 45, Box 24)
  - Greenville High School, 1996 (Folder 46, Box 24)
  - Hagley [Museum and Library], 1991 - 1996 (Folder 1, Box 25)
  - Holt, Rinehart & Winston, 1996 (Folder 2, Box 25)
  - Hoover P - L [Presidential Library], 1991 - 1997 (Folder 3, Box 25)
  - HRHRC [Harry Ransom Humanities Research Center, The University of Texas at Austin], 1991 (Folder 4, Box 25)
  - Imperial War Museum, 1991 - 1996 (Folder 5, Box 25)
  - Interior [Department] (FOIA) [Freedom of Information Act], 1993 (Folder 6, Box 25)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson P - L [Presidential Library], 1991 (Folder 7, Box 25)
  - Justice [Department] (FBI) [Freedom of Information Act], 1993 - 1998 (Folder 8, Box 25)
  - Claire Keith, 1996 - 1998 (Folder 9, Box 25)
  - Edward M. Kennedy, 1991 - 1992 (Folder 10, Box 25)
  - John F. Kennedy P - L [Presidential Library], 1991 (Folder 11, Box 25)
  - King's College, London, 1991 (Folder 12, Box 25)
  - Kirkman (Montang), 1997 (Folder 13, Box 25)
  - LHC for MA (Kings's College), 1988 - 1994 (Folder 14, Box 25)
  - University of London, 1988 (Folder 15, Box 25)
  - Marine Corps Library, 1996 (Folder 16, Box 25)
  - Marist [College], 1991 - 1996 (Folder 17, Box 25)
  - Marist [College], [also Penn State?], 1992 - 1994 (Folder 18, Box 25)
  - Wayne McCormick, 1997 (Folder 19, Box 25)
  - Ministry of Defence, 1989 - 1993 (Folder 20, Box 25)
  - Movietone Newsfilm Library [University of South Carolina], 1991 - 1996 (Folder 21, Box 25)
  - MSU Vincent Voice Library [Michigan State University], 1996 - 1997 (Folder 22, Box 25)
  - Mugar (Boston) [Boston University Library], 1996 (Folder 23, Box 25)
  - Museum of Television & Radio, 1991 - 1996 (Folder 24, Box 25)
  - NARA [National Archives and Records Administration], 1996 - 1997 (Folder 25, Box 25)
  - National Press Club, 1996 (Folder 26, Box 25)
  - Navy (FOIA) [Freedom of Information Act], 1993 - 1994 (Folder 27, Box 25)
  - NBC, 1996 (Folder 28, Box 25)
  - Nebraska [University of Nebraska Medical Center], 1997 (Folder 29, Box 25)
  - New Jersey (SSS), 1996 - 1997 (Folder 30, Box 25)
  - New York Public Library, 1991 (Folder 31, Box 25)
  - New York Times Book Review, 1990 - 1991 (Folder 1, Box 26)
  - Richard M. Nixon, 1991 (Folder 2, Box 26)
  - Nixon P - M [Presidential Library], 1991 (Folder 3, Box 26)
  - Old Time Radio, 1996 (Folder 4, Box 26)
  - Palladour (Powell), 1991 (Folder 5, Box 26)
  - Pawling Free Library, 1991 (Folder 6, Box 26)
  - Princeton Archives (Mudd), 1991 (Folder 7, Box 26)
  - Procter & Gamble, 1996 (Folder 8, Box 26)
  - Radio Yesteryear, 1996 (Folder 9, Box 26)
  - Reader's Digest, 1997 (Folder 10, Box 26)
  - Ronald W. Reagan, 1991 - 1996 (Folder 11, Box 26)
  - Reagan P - L [Presidential Library], 1991 (Folder 12, Box 26)
  - Regnery Gateway [Hoover Institute], 1988 (Folder 13, Box 26)
  - Roosevelt P - L [FDR Presidential Library, 1991 - 1993 (Folder 14, Box 26)
  - RUSI/Corbett [Royal United Services Institute for Defence Studies], 1989 (Folder 15, Box 26)
  - SATW [Society of American Travel Writers], 1997 (Folder 16, Box 26)
  - School District #1 (Victor), 1996 (Folder 17, Box 26)
  - Selective Service System, 1996 (Folder 18, Box 26)
  - Simon & Schuster, 1996 (Folder 19, Box 26)
  - Truman P - L [Presidential Library], 1991 (Folder 20, Box 26)
  - State [Department] (FOIA) [Freedom of Information Act], 1994 - 1996 (Folder 21, Box 26)
  - Sun Oil, 1991 (Folder 22, Box 26)
  - University of Denver (& Penrose), 1991 - 1996 (Folder 23, Box 26)
  - Utah (David Gardner) [University of Utah], 1997 (Folder 24, Box 26)
  - Valparaiso [University], 1991 - 1997 (Folder 25, Box 26)
  - Vermont Council (Ski), 1996 (Folder 26, Box 26)
  - Victor Public Library, 1991 (Folder 27, Box 26)
  - Victor / LT Museum [Lowell Thomas Museum], 1991 (Folder 28, Box 26)
  - Will Rogers Museum, 1991 (Folder 29, Box 26)
  - Wisconsin Historical Society Mass Commo CTR, 1996 (Folder 30, Box 26)
  - [Francis] Yeats - Brown, 1996 (Folder 31, Box 26)
- 5. External Research File, 5; Boxes: 27 - 51
  - A - bomb, 1964 (Folder 1, Box 27)
  - A - bomb book, 1967 September 28 (Folder 2, Box 27)
  - Abu Dhabi (Vanocer), 1969 (Folder 3, Box 27)
  - Abu Simbel (Nubian), 1960 - 1966 (Folder 4, Box 27)
  - Adelphi (Comm SPCH), 1951 October 3 (Folder 5, Box 27)
  - Adirondack 19750605, 1975 - 1997 (Folder 6, Box 27)
  - Adventurers Club, 1934 (Folder 7, Box 27)
  - Advertising Club - Hom?, 1937 (Folder 8, Box 27)
  - Alaska, 1963 - 1974 (Folder 9, Box 27)
  - Alien Ink, by Natalie Robins, 1992 (Folder 10, Box 27)
  - Alsop, 1948 (Folder 11, Box 27)
  - American Colony, 1962 - 1993 (Folder 12, Box 27)
  - American Colony Chronology, undated (Folder 13, Box 27)
  - The American Radio, by Llewellyn White, 1947 (Folder 14, Box 27)
  - Gleason L. Archer, 1971 (Folder 15, Box 27)
  - Ascap, 1941 (Folder 16, Box 27)
  - Asia, 1996 (Folder 17, Box 27)
  - Asia - Froelick (NARA) [National Archives and Records Administration], 1925 (Folder 18, Box 27)
  - Asia - T. E. Lawrence, 1919 - 1926 (Folder 19, Box 27)
  - Isaac Asimov, 1980 (Folder 20, Box 27)
  - Mohammad Ata - Ullah, 1960 (Folder 21, Box 27)
  - The Atlantic, 1936 April (Folder 22, Box 27)
  - Atwater, 1968 (Folder 1, Box 28)
  - Audience, 1938 (Folder 2, Box 28)
  - Australia (NARA), 1921 (Folder 3, Box 28)
  - Australia National Library, circa 1919 (Folder 4, Box 28)
  - Australia National Library, circa 1919 (Folder 5, Box 28)
  - Australian Film: 1900 - 1977, by Andrew Pike and Ross Cooper, 1980 (Folder 6, Box 28)
  - Back to Mandalay, 1950 - 1951 (Folder 7, Box 28)
  - Banquet - "A Salute to Lowell Thomas", 1965 (Folder 8, Box 28)
  - Eric Barnouw, Media Marathon, 1996 (Folder 9, Box 28)
  - Eric Barnouw, Documentary, 1974 (Folder 10, Box 28)
  - Erik Barnouw, The Sponsor, 1978 (Folder 11, Box 28)
  - Eric Barnouw, Tube of Plenty, 1990 (Folder 12, Box 28)
  - Marvin Barrett, Survey of Broadcast Journalism, 1970 - 1971 (Folder 13, Box 28)
  - The Bob Bartlett Papers (Bowdoin College Library), 1938 - 193 (Folder 14, Box 28)
  - Bruce Barton (Bowdoin College Library), 1937 (Folder 15, Box 28)
  - James L. Baughman, Television's Guardians, 1985 (Folder 16, Box 28)
  - Rex Beach, The Spoilers, 1969 (Folder 17, Box 28)
  - Sir Thomas Beecham, 1952 (Folder 18, Box 28)
  - Clyde Beatty, 1934 (Folder 19, Box 28)
  - Beaverbrook, 1996 (Folder 20, Box 28)
  - Marvin R. Bensman, Broadcast Regulation, 1985 (Folder 21, Box 28)
  - Best Years, 1980 (Folder 22, Box 28)
  - Hugh Malcolm Beville, Jr., Audience Ratings: Radio, Television, and Cable, 1985 (Folder 23, Box 28)
  - Beyond Khyber Pass, 1925 (Folder 24, Box 28)
  - Birthday, 1972 (Folder 25, Box 28)
  - Birth house, 1987 (Folder 26, Box 28)
  - Jim Bishop, 1957 (Folder 27, Box 28)
  - Ed Bliss, 1953 - 1981 (Folder 28, Box 28)
  - Bodleian Library, Oxford University, 1920 (Folder 29, Box 28)
  - Bloopers, 1984 (Folder 30, Box 28)
  - Bohemian Grove, 1933 - 1993 (Folder 1, Box 29)
  - Book of the High Mountains, circa 1964 - 1993 (Folder 2, Box 29)
  - Book Review Digest, 1924 - 1979 (Folder 3, Box 29)
  - Booker Birth house photograph, circa 1981 (Folder 4, Box 29)
  - Booker Cuttings [originals], 1892 - 1996 (Folder 5, Box 29)
  - Booker Cuttings [photocopies], 1892 - 1996 (Folder 6, Box 29)
  - Booker - Lowell Thomas file, 1986 - 1987 (Folder 7, Box 29)
  - [Bill] Booker Research [originals], 1939 - 1990 (Folder 8, Box 29)
  - [Bill] Booker Research [photocopies], 1939 - 1990 (Folder 9, Box 29)
  - Boys' Life, 1927 (Folder 10, Box 29)
  - Berton Braley, 1939 - 1950 (Folder 11, Box 29)
  - David Brinkley, 1995 (Folder 12, Box 29)
  - Broadcast Archives, 1983 (Folder 1, Box 30)
  - Broadcast Pioneers, 1965 - 1968 (Folder 2, Box 30)
  - Tom Brokaw, 1995 (Folder 3, Box 30)
  - Les Brown, Television: The Business Behind the Box, 1971 (Folder 4, Box 30)
  - James Buchan, circa 1989 (Folder 5, Box 30)
  - William Buckley, 1995 September 17 (Folder 6, Box 30)
  - Prosper Buranelli (National Union Catalog), undated (Folder 7, Box 30)
  - Burke correspondence, 1963 July (Folder 8, Box 30)
  - Burma Jack, 1971 (Folder 9, Box 30)
  - George H. W. Bush, 1982 - 1991 (Folder 10, Box 30)
  - Smedley D. Butler, 1935 - 1991 (Folder 11, Box 30)
  - Karen S. Buzzard, Chains of Gold: Marketing the Ratings and Rating the Markets, 1990 (Folder 12, Box 30)
  - Brigham Young University, 1951 - 1973 (Folder 13, Box 30)
  - Capital Cities, 1963 - 1996 (Folder 14, Box 30)
  - Capital Cities Broadcasting Corp. - Legal affairs, 1953 - 1957 (Folder 15, Box 30)
  - Dale Carnegie [Carnagey], 1936 - 1964 (Folder 16, Box 30)
  - Ralph Carr, 1940 (Folder 17, Box 30)
  - Ralph Carr Papers, 1938 - 1942 (Folder 18, Box 30)
  - Boake Carter, 1937 (Folder 1, Box 31)
  - Jimmy Carter P - L [Presidential Library], 1977 - 1978 (Folder 2, Box 31)
  - Cassini (Knickerbacker), 1965 December 18 (Folder 3, Box 31)
  - Harry Castleman and Walter J. Podrazik, Watching TV: Four Decades of American Television, 1982 (Folder 4, Box 31)
  - The Challenge of Change, by Arthur M. Johnson, 1983 (Folder 5, Box 31)
  - Matthew N. Chappell and C. E. Hooper, Radio Audience Measurement, 1944 (Folder 6, Box 31)
  - Chi Gents [Chicago Gentlemen, Arthur Mecker of Armour & Co.], 1917 - 1981 (Folder 7, Box 31)
  - Child Labor, 1935 (Folder 8, Box 31)
  - Francis Chase, Jr., Sound and Fury: An Informal History of Broadcasting, 1942 (Folder 9, Box 31)
  - Christ Church, 1987 - 1991 (Folder 10, Box 31)
  - Connie Chung, 1995 (Folder 11, Box 31)
  - CIA [Central Intelligence Agency], 1995 (Folder 12, Box 31)
  - Cincinnati, 1893 - 1894 (Folder 13, Box 31)
  - Cinerama (19521001), 1951 - 1997 (Folder 14, Box 31)
  - Cinerama - Damascus, 1954 (Folder 15, Box 31)
  - Cinerama (Fortune), 1953 (Folder 16, Box 31)
  - Cinerama Inventory, undated (Folder 17, Box 31)
  - Cinerama - Indus, 1985 (Folder 18, Box 31)
  - Cinerama - Opening notes, 1952 (Folder 19, Box 31)
  - Cinerama - Programs, undated (Folder 20, Box 31)
  - Cinerama - Revival, 1996 - 1997 (Folder 21, Box 31)
  - Cinerama Revival - Wide gauge film, 1997 (Folder 22, Box 31)
  - Claremont (Honnold), 1926 - 1975 (Folder 23, Box 31)
  - Neil Clarke, 1924 (1997) (Folder 1, Box 32)
  - Harry Cohn - King Cohn: The Life and Times of Harry Cohn, by Bob Thomas, 1967 (Folder 2, Box 32)
  - Cold War, 1996 (Folder 3, Box 32)
  - Cold War News (George Seldes), 1949 (Folder 4, Box 32)
  - Colorado Ski Hall of Fame, 1978 - 1979 (Folder 5, Box 32)
  - Columbia Oral History, 1970 - 1988 (Folder 6, Box 32)
  - Comfort (Booker), undated (Folder 7, Box 32)
  - Congress, 1933 - 1966 (Folder 8, Box 32)
  - Congressional Record, 1939 - 1982 (Folder 9, Box 32)
  - Coronation, 1937 (Folder 10, Box 32)
  - Eddie Connellan, 1966 - 1992 (Folder 11, Box 32)
  - Conventions (TV), 1952 - 1995 (Folder 12, Box 32)
  - 1929 Crash, 1995 (Folder 13, Box 32)
  - Fred C. Crawford, 1959 (Folder 14, Box 32)
  - George Creel, How We Advertised America, 1920 (Folder 15, Box 32)
  - Walter Cronkite, 1981 (Folder 16, Box 32)
  - David H. Culbert, News for Everyman: Radio and Foreign Affairs in Thirties America, 1976 (Folder 17, Box 32)
  - Daniel J. Czitrom, Media and the American Mind, 1982 (Folder 18, Box 32)
  - Clarence Darrow, 1932 - 1979 (Folder 19, Box 32)
  - Dartmouth, 1948 (Folder 20, Box 32)
  - Decline, undated (Folder 21, Box 32)
  - Scott Deindorfer, Dear Scott, 1978 (Folder 22, Box 32)
  - Thomas A. DeLong, Radio Stars: An Illustrated Biographical Dictionary of 953 Performers, 1920 though 1960, 1996 (Folder 23, Box 32)
  - Denver Days, 1912 - 1913 (Folder 24, Box 32)
  - Denver PL [Public Library] (Roberson) [includes correspondence with Lowell Thomas and Harry Chase], circa 1913 - 1917 (Folder 25, Box 32)
  - Denver P - L [Public Library] Cuttings [clippings], 1909 - 1990 (Folder 26, Box 32)
  - University of Denver, Penrose - Real Property Appraisal, Lowell Thomas Estate, 1975 (Folder 1, Box 33)
  - University of Denver, Penrose - Lowell Thomas Law Center, Chancellor Mitchell Papers box 17, 1975 (Folder 2, Box 33)
  - University of Denver, Penrose - Buildings: University Hall Renovation, 1979 - 1988 (Folder 3, Box 33)
  - University of Denver, Penrose - Buildings: University Hall fundraising, 1978 - 1979 (Folder 4, Box 33)
  - University of Denver, Penrose - Buildings: Lowell Thomas Law Building, 1974 - 1983 (Folder 5, Box 33)
  - University of Denver / Hammersly Hill, 1987 (Folder 6, Box 33)
  - University of Denver, Penrose - Chronology (index cards), 1944 - 1982 (Folder 7, Box 33)
  - University of Denver, Penrose - (Mr. and Mrs.) Lowell J. Thomas, 1953 - 1962 (Folder 8, Box 33)
  - University of Denver, Penrose - Lowell Thomas correspondence, 1969 - 1978 (Folder 9, Box 33)
  - University of Denver, Penrose - Lowell Thomas, 1969 - 1976 (Folder 10, Box 33)
  - University of Denver, Penrose - Lowell Thomas, " A Tribute to Tibet ", 1975 - 1976 May (Folder 11, Box 33)
  - Thomas E. Dewey, 1944 - 1982 (Folder 12, Box 33)
  - Thomas E. Dewey and His Times, Richard Norton Smith, 1982 (Folder 13, Box 33)
  - " Dewey 's Pawling, " Life Magazine, 1944 September 11 (Folder 14, Box 33)
  - Dionne Quintuplets, 1994 - 1996 (Folder 15, Box 33)
  - Dogs, 1995 (Folder 16, Box 33)
  - Minot (Minnie) Dole, Adventures in Skiing; Forward by Lowell Thomas, 1965 (Folder 1, Box 34)
  - Dollar Value Conversion, 1800 - 1995 (Folder 2, Box 34)
  - Jimmy Doolittle, 1930 - 1993 (Folder 3, Box 34)
  - Susan J. Douglas, Inventing American Broadcasting, 1899 - 1992, 1987 (Folder 4, Box 34)
  - Dukore, undated (Folder 5, Box 34)
  - Allen Dulles (Mudd Manuscript Library, Princeton), 1950 - 1969 (Folder 6, Box 34)
  - John Foster Dulles (Mudd Manuscript Library, Princeton), 1952 - 1957 (Folder 7, Box 34)
  - John Dunning, Tune in Yesterday, 1976 (Folder 8, Box 34)
  - Walter Duranty, I Write as I Please, 1935 (Folder 9, Box 34)
  - Dutch Treat Club, 1980 (Folder 10, Box 34)
  - Early Radio, 1935 - 1997 (Folder 11, Box 34)
  - Early Radio (Broadcasting), 1982 (Folder 12, Box 34)
  - Early Radio - The Early Days of Radio Broadcasting, by George H. Douglas, 1987 (Folder 13, Box 34)
  - Early Radio (Howe), 1957 (Folder 14, Box 34)
  - Early Radio: Sam J. Slate and Joe Cook, It Sounds Impossible, 1963 (Folder 15, Box 34)
  - Early Radio chronology (Ditingo), 1995 (Folder 16, Box 34)
  - Early Radio news, 1939 - 1943 (Folder 17, Box 34)
  - Early Television, 1940 (Folder 18, Box 34)
  - Susan Tyler Eastman, et. al., Broadcast Programming: Strategies for Winning Television and Radio Audiences, 1981 (Folder 19, Box 34)
  - Eastman Kodak, 1996 (Folder 20, Box 34)
  - Eisenhower Papers, 1984 (Folder 21, Box 34)
  - Eisenhower P - L [Presidential Library], 1945 - 1959 (Folder 1, Box 35)
  - Frank Elkins, 1954 (Folder 2, Box 35)
  - Eminent Georgians: The Lives of King George V, Elizabeth Bowen, St. John Philby & Nancy Astor, by John Halpern, 1995 (Folder 3, Box 35)
  - Edward Jay Epstein, News from Nowhere, 1973 (Folder 4, Box 35)
  - Empire State Building, 1995 (Folder 5, Box 35)
  - Executive Action: Assassination of a Head of State, by Donald Freed and Mark Lane, 1973 (Folder 6, Box 35)
  - Explorer's Club, 1947 - 1997 (Folder 7, Box 35)
  - Explorers Club Tales, 1936 (Folder 8, Box 35)
  - Fair Game, Denis Brian, 1994 (Folder 9, Box 35)
  - Family Stuff [Lowell Thomas Biographical Notes], 1976 (Folder 10, Box 35)
  - FCC [United States Federal Communication Commission], 1938 - 1962 (Folder 11, Box 35)
  - Raymond Fielding, The American Newsfeel, 1911 - 1967, 1972 (Folder 12, Box 35)
  - Raymond Fielding, The March of Time, 1935 - 1951, 1978 (Folder 13, Box 35)
  - Fight for Freedom, Inc., 1941 (Folder 1, Box 36)
  - Film (Lumieres), 1996 (Folder 2, Box 36)
  - Fireplace, 1950 (Folder 3, Box 36)
  - First Aid for Backpackers and Campers, Lowell J. Thomas & Jay L. Sanderson, 1979 (Folder 4, Box 36)
  - Hamilton Fish, 1933 - 1992 (Folder 5, Box 36)
  - FOIA [Freedom of Information Act] - NARA [National Archives and Records Administration], 1992 (Folder 6, Box 36)
  - Rosita Forbes, 1923 - 1990 (Folder 7, Box 36)
  - Gerald Ford, 1974 - 1979 (Folder 8, Box 36)
  - Gerald Ford P - L [Presidential Library], 1975 - 1977 (Folder 9, Box 36)
  - Henry Ford, 1957 (Folder 10, Box 36)
  - James Forrestal (Mudd Manuscript Library, Princeton), 1946 (Folder 11, Box 36)
  - Ann Fox Anecdote, 1995 (Folder 12, Box 36)
  - The Franklin Mint, 1997 (Folder 13, Box 36)
  - Fraternity Row, 1963 (Folder 14, Box 36)